<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 14:15:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/home/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 14:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/home/home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;block text&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/Homepage.png&#34; alt=&#34;homelogo&#34; &gt;&lt;/center&gt;&#xA;    &lt;center&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;u&gt;About Me&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&#xA;    &lt;H4&gt;Hello! I’m Jeremy Drag, a dedicated cybersecurity student at Millikin University with a passion for coding and problem-solving. With a strong academic record, including a 3.98 GPA and numerous honors, I have developed proficiency in languages such as Java, JavaScript, and Python. My experiences range from interning at Constellation Nuclear Power, where I contribute to building efficient database displays, to working in performance consulting, helping clients with web and database solutions. I thrive in fast-paced environments, utilizing my leadership skills to train peers and support users at the Millikin IT Helpdesk. &lt;/H4&gt;&#xA;   &lt;center&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;u&gt; What is this website meant for?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&#xA;    &lt;H4&gt;This website is being built for a capstone project but is also meant to give an idea about some of the hobbies that I have. The Play a Game page allows you to play Snake which is one of the first games that I learned how to make. Additionally, there is a portfolio page that gives you a look into my hobby of photography where you can see some of the pictures that I have taken for various events.&lt;/H4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;H4&gt;The website itself was built using Hugo for a base static website and then I edited the theme accordingly to make it my own.&lt;/H4&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
